# CRAIG HENDERSON

Manchester, UK; M36ES

Phone: +44(0)7507 059473 | Email: lionwolfgroup@gmail.com

LinkedIn: LinkedIn\_ Github: Github

#### SUMMARY

Passionate about life in general, particularly passionate about Finance, Fintech, and Blockchain. I have a life-long dedication to learning and self-improvement. Experienced entrepreneur with a background in sales, business development, marketing, social media marketing, start-up consultation, project management, and fundraising

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages: HTML; Javascript; CSS; Node JS; SQL

**Vertical Knowledge**: Financial Markets; Web3; Blockchain; Fintech; Metaverse; NFTs;; B2B sales; Digital Marketing; Social Media Marketing; Email Marketing Business Development, Start-Ups; Community Building; Fund Raising

**Platforms**: Google Workspace; Microsoft Office Excel; Google Analytics, CRMs, Hubspot, Mailchimp, Buffer; Microsoft Teams, Slack Monday.com; Asana, IFTTT; LinkedIn Sales Navigator; Canva

**Social Media Platforms**: Discord; Telegram; Twitter; Twitter Spaces; Facebook; LinkedIn; Instagram; Youtube; Reddit; Tik Tok; WhatsApp; Snapchat; Quora

**EXPERIENCE** 

## **Advisor/Business Development**

2020 - Present

#### Whalemaker

Key responsibilities include consultation on launching a startup incubator/launchpad. Advised on the tokenomics structure, white paper, pitch deck formation, analysis of market conditions, coming up with a marketing strategy, identifying projects to onboard, and partnerships as well as investor outreach

#### Key Accomplishments:

 Helped to bring the project from an idea to currently having an MVP. Created communities on Discord and Telegram and launched an initial marketing campaign and whitelisting campaign. NFT creation.

## **Marketing Manager**

2019 - 2020

#### Finxflo

Managing all marketing for the company and activities within the marketing department. Developing the marketing strategy for the company in line with company objectives. Coordinating marketing campaigns with sales activities. Overseeing the company's marketing budget. Business development and strategic partner outreach.

## Key Accomplishments:

• Helped to raise 2.7 million dollars via private fundraising, followed by a successful token launch via IDO on Polkastarter

### **Business Development Specialist**

2019 - 2020

## Bounty0x

Was responsible for identifying promising projects, educating them on the benefits of hosting a bounty campaign on Bounty0x, and onboarding them. Duties included creation and management of bounty campaigns as well as keeping track of important KPIs

## **Community Manager**

2018 - 2019

#### **ITAM Games**

My responsibilities included managing, engaging, and growing the community. I lead a team that communicated with the ITAM Community, answering any questions users may have, sharing content and updates regarding ITAM Games, hosting competitions and giveaways, and being the forefront representative of ITAM Games.

#### Key Accomplishments:

• Helped to build both Telegram and Discord communities from the ground up to having several thousand members on each Platform.

(ISA)Independent Contractor

2015 - 2018

#### **Appointments Today**

#### Key Accomplishments:

• Worked with Realtors Nationwide(USA) to increase sales, and schedule face-to-face appointments. I worked with all kinds of clients from F.S.B.O's Expireds, Sellers, and Buyers. Probate Leads. Was responsible for increasing sales by hundreds of millions of dollars.

#### **EDUCATION**

Year: 2022

University of Manchester, Boot Camp Certificate

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js, and ReactJS.

Year: 2016

Yale University: Financial Markets; Coursera online Certificate

An overview of the ideas, methods, and institutions that permit human society to manage risks and foster enterprise. Emphasis on financially-savvy leadership skills. Description of practices today and analysis of prospects for the future. Introduction to risk management and behavioral finance principles to understand the real-world functioning of securities, insurance, and banking industries.

Year: 2006 -2007

**Bermuda College** 

Certificate in Construction Management